Failure? What is that?
Fracasso? O que é?
Oh right, I've heard about that.
Certo, já ouvi falar sobre isso.
It's such a simple, such a cliché thing. You can't succeed without failure.
É uma coisa tão simples, tão clichê. Não é possível ter sucesso sem falhar alguma vez.
For me venturing on is hopefully a lifestyle.
Para mim, ser destemido, arriscar é um modo de estar na vida.
It's this idea of constantly discovering, constantly being curious and constantly hoping that the road has no end.
Significa estar constantemente a descobrir, ser sempre curioso e manter a esperança de que o caminho não tem fim.
I'm curious about things. I'm curious about the world, about different cultures, about different kinds of people,
Tenho curiosidade pelas coisas. Curioso pelo mundo, pelas diferentes culturas, pelos diferentes tipos de pessoas.
and it's my curiosity and my selfishness of wanting to find that out about myself,
E é a minha curiosidade e o meu egoísmo que me impelem a saber mais sobre mim mesmo,
that drives me to do new kinds of projects.
que me motiva para novos projetos.
I'm very lucky though that I've been able to build an audience that goes on that trip with me.
Tenho muita sorte em ter encontrado um público que me acompanha nesta jornada.
In some ways I like to be very prepared and study and learn about it and figure out what my point of view is going to be.
Gosto de estar preparado, de analisar e de aprender, para conhecer a minha perspetiva sobre algo de novo.
But I also don't want to know too much.
Mas também não quero saber demais.
I kind of always approach it in two ways, being somewhat prepared and somewhat ready just to be surprised.
Geralmente, utilizo duas abordagens : estar um pouco preparado, mas também aberto a surpresas.